good morning.
おはようございます
お はようございます
Did Tama go?
タマは行けた?
were you cold?
お前は寒かったの?
Oh, really, there are insect shells flying around.
あ、 ほんとだ、 なんか虫殻が飛んでるね
ERROR
俺もさ、ここに虫殻を飛んできたし、
I touched an insect shell today, and it was supposed to be like this, and an insect shell came flying at me.
今日虫殻タッチこんなはずで、 虫殻を飛んできたよ
Insect shells flying?
虫殻飛んでる?
That's why I want you to fly away in your insect shell.
だからさ、 お前虫殻で飛んできてもらいたいなと
What should I do?
どうしようかな?
First of all, is that it?
まずは、あれかな?
First of all, are you laughing?
まずは、笑いっこかな?
I wonder how many I have to do, after all.
何個しないとね、やっぱりね
I need to drink something.
何か飲まないと
Was it cold?
寒かった?
Congratulations.
おめでとう
I'll feed you, so watch this.
食べてあげるから、これ見て
I'm going home.
帰るね
I'm going home, uncle.
帰るだから、おじさんさ
Uncle, try it.
おじさん、食べてみて
Uncle, I have to drink.
お じ さん、 飲 まないと
Uncle, you're good at washing.
おじさん、洗うのうまいから
Here, you have to wash to get under the salt.
ここね、塩の下についてまで洗わないといけないから
I need to wash the tip a little.
先端のところ、ちょっと洗わないと
Uncle, below.
おじさん、下のね
Because the bottom one is better.
下の方がいいから
Here.
ここね
Is it okay if I push the water up?
水を押し上げたら、いいの?
If you push the water up,
水 を押し上げたら、
Is it okay?
いい の?
Uncle, you don't want to make a mess after washing.
おじさん、洗った後、汚してくさいから
Uncle, I want you to wash your clothes when you're an uncle.
おじさん、おじさんの時、洗ってほしいな
Uncle, just a little
おじさんは、ちょっと
Can I have it washed away?
流 してもらっていいかな?
A little inside Okinawa.
沖縄の中まで、ちょっと
We have to flush it all the way into Okinawa.
沖縄の中まで、流さないと
Uncle, this is the style that will make a mess if you wash it.
おじさん、これ、流したら汚していくスタイルだから
Next time, I'll have you wash your mouth.
次、口で洗ってもらおうかな
Have them wash their mouths.
口で洗ってもらって
This hand.
こっちの手
Firmly, firmly.
しっかり、しっかり
Properly deep inside.
奥までちゃんと
This hand.
こっちの手
That's right, peek from below and see where you are.
そうそう、下から覗いて、 自分が入っているところ
You can leave it like this.
このまましちゃっていいよね
You can see yourself from below.
下から覗ける、自分が出ているところ
It's really dripping right now.
今、めっちゃ垂れちゃってる
It'll come out again.
また出てくる
Uncle, I'm going home now that I've skinned it.
おじさん、スキンしたから帰るね
I took a shower and then again.
私、シャワーかけちゃって、また
thank you.
ありがとう